pakistanway.com 2008-06-21

# Pakistanway - Privacy Policy

| **Private Policy**  
---  
Pakistanway is committed to the privacy of its members. Pakistanway utilizes a high degree of encryption on information sent over the Internet and on information stored within its system. The following policies outline other specific protections that Pakistanway has in place.  
**Member Registration**  
One must be at least 13 years of age to become a member of Pakistanway sites. When you register with Pakistanway, you will be asked to provide certain information about yourself and your interests. This information includes how to contact you and basic demographic and lifestyle information. Pakistanway uses this information to learn more about its audience and to provide you with the content and information most attuned to your interests. This information may be shared with reputable third parties who wish to send you information by email or postal mail. You may update any personal information on this profile page as well.  
**Child Protection Policy**  
One must be at least 13 years of age to register with Pakistanway. It is Pakistanway policy to neither accept nor store any registrations or other personal information from children under the age of 13.  
**Option to Receive / not to Receive Mail**  
Pakistanway is pleased to be able to bring you extra value by providing you information and offers specific to your interests. Some of these communications are opt-in only. You will only receive emails containing your interested offers. You may change your interests at any time by logging into the Pakistanway site and editing your member profile. Other mailings or offers are related specifically to your Pakistanway account or the Pakistanway site. By maintaining your Pakistanway account, you grant Pakistanway permission to contact you with these offers and information.  
**Sharing the Information with Third Parties**  
Pakistanway may transfer the user's Information to merchants and advertisers who promote different products and services throughout the site. We use an outside ad company to display ads on our websites. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web sites, our ad company collects cookies received from banner ads, and we do not have access to this information.  
We may disclose Personal Information to other people or agencies in order to (a) follow the law or comply with legal process served on our affiliates; (b) protect and defend our rights or property or those of our users, and (c) act as quickly as needed to protect the personal safety of our users or other people.  
**Security**  
Pakistanway sites has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  
**Cancellation**  
At any point you wish us to remove your profile from the Pakistanway sites, you may cancel your account. Following a holding period to ensure that your account was not mistakenly cancelled, your account will be deleted and all personal information will be permanently removed from the Pakistanway sites.  
Pakistanway is committed to maintaining the highest standards of privacy. We reserve the right to modify these policies at any time. Notification of any such changes will be posted on [ www.pakistanway.com](http://www.pakistanway.com/)  
For more information you can contact us at [ info @ pakistanway.com](mailto:info@pakistanway.com)
